Matt Golino

Experience Designer

Objective

Pursuing an internship that will challenge me to create exciting user experiences with state of the art technology such as VR and AR, while providing the opportunity to learn and grow through teamwork with other skilled designers.

Skills

Design

InVision Balsamiq Adobe XD Sketch Photoshop Illustrator InDesign Wireframes Storyboards User Journey Concept Sketching Paper Prototype Wizard-of-Oz

Research

Survey
Participatory Design
User Interview
Usability Testing
Card Sort
Affinity Mapping

Development

Unity Engine Arduino
HTML Raspberry Pi
CSS MBED

Javascript Command Line Git
AngularJS Bitbucket
ReactJS GitLab
JQuery Github
C++ Subversion

C XML
Assembly JSON
Java JSP
Python MATLAB

Communication

Public Speaking
Whiteboarding
Group Brainstorming
Workshop Events
Technical Documentation

Awards

Eagle Scout Atlanta Interactive Marketing Association Scholarship Mock Trial Attorney Award

Education

Georgia Insitute of Technology

MS in Human-Computer Interaction Expected Graduation: May 2020

BS Computer Engineering Graduation Date: May 2016

Notable Courses

VR Studio
Visualizing Interaction
Visual Design
Interactive Products ID Studio
Video Game Design
Research Methods for HCI
HCI Foundations

www.linkedin.com/in/matthew.golino

(917)-767-4011 mgolino16@gmail.com www.MattGolino.com

Project Experience

Bookr

Fall 2018

Researched user needs and designed a mobile app to help connect musicians with venues. This project has currently been picked up by a small record label for continued development and eventual launch.

Moe's Voice Ordering System

Fall 2018

Partnered with Moe's Southwest Grill to research the efficacy of a voice ordering system. Research findings were then used to build a machine learning based prototype and conduct user testing with experts.

Illuso

Fall 2018

Designed and developed a 3rd person "game feel" video game in Unity.
Conducted subsequent user testing and iterated on the design.

Work Experience

TextBuddy

Fall 2018

Designed a mobile application and voice interface to help commuter students listen to their textbooks on-the-go. Protoyped interface mockups and a wizard-of-oz demo to showcase the design at appropriate fidelity.

Balance Sensory Alert Device

Spring 2016

Implemented a wearable fall-detection device for users with impaired balance. Project won 1st place in Computer Engineering at the Georgia Tech 2016 Capstone Design competition.

Infinity

Spring 2016 Created a music-reactive infinity mirror experience and accompanying mobile app for finetuned user control.

Front-end Web Developer/UI Specialist | General Motors

August 2016 - August 2018

- -Worked on multiple Agile development teams to create user-facing retail web applications accessed by thousands of car dealerships daily
- -Designed and wireframed webpage mockups and built relevant assets
- -Implemented HTML, CSS, and Javascript webpages using AngularJS and ReactJS frameworks in a cross-browser setting

Mobile Development Intern | SapientNitro

June 2015 - August 2015

-Designed and implemented an interactive menu using the infrared motion detection of the Leap Motion to capture user interaction -Researched, implemented, and customized a digital signage CMS for networked management of in-office media displays

Software Development Intern | Gartner

June 2014 - August 2014 & January 2015 - May 2015

-Helped design and implement various Java/J2EE web components to be used in the launch of a new internal CMS